Everyday is a compromise
Everyday I am struggling
Can I follow you 'round the day for my soul?
Did you know that I want you here?
Did you know that I hear the change for us?
Did you know when you stared at me cold?
And we'll look back in the dark
The memories all around
I wish I could hide in the past
Over the space
Well only the stars can help me now
Only the stars can save me (save me, save me)
Everyday is a compromise
Everyday I am struggling
Is it something that can make me stable?
Do you think you will be happy now?
Do you think you can talk to me someday?
I will throw it all into the flames
When I look back in the dark
The memories all around
I wish I could hide in the past
Over the space
Well only the stars can help me now
Only the stars can save me (save me, save me)
Save me, save me
Only these stars can save me (save me, save me)
Everyday is a compromise
Everyday I am struggling
Is there something that can make me stable?